Welcome back and have a look.
Time for a dark theater.
Bug War
This is a story about a child spending his summer vacation at his grandfather's house.
Go for it!
I want a stronger bug.
If we're gonna catch him, doesn't it have to be at night?
Night...
They won't let me leave the room.
I wonder which bug will win.
Either way.
it's sure to be a great match.
The adults hold special insect sumo matches at night.
I want to see, I want to see!
I want to see, I want to see, I want to see, I want to see!
No guests.
Give me back last year's money.
Okay, last one.
Let's get into it.
Come on, come on
Step right up, to the bug arena.
Go!
Do it!
Don't lose!
There's a lot of money at stake.
Who's that brat over there?
Hey!
Wait!
hey, hey!
This isn't what we agreed on.
Gyaa!
Don't come!
Kyou...
I'm sorry, Grandpa.
i didn't mean to see it.
I thought it was still too soon for you. But...
you saw it. Well, it can't be helped.
Next year's insect sumo,
Do you want to try?
Eh?
Is it ok?
The end